HILLOL DAS PIAS

WEB DEVELOPER



- +8801738206419
- ✓ hillol4958@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/hillol-daspias-56454bb1
- https://github.com/HillolPias
- Park Gate, Betia Para, House no.35, Rajpara, Rajshahi

PROFILE

I am a qualified Full Stack Developer with three years of experience in coding and graphic design and 1.5 years of experience in both front-end and back-end development. I possess strong creative and analytical skills, and I am a collaborative team player with a keen eye for detail and a passion for building efficient and scalable web applications.

SKILLS

- Full-Stack: Next.js v15 (App Router, SSG, SSR, API Routes)
- Front-end: React.js v19 (Context API, Redux-Toolkit, React-Router v7 etc.)
- Back-end: Node.js, Express.js, REST APIs etc.
- TypeScript/JavaScript
- Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB,
 SQLite etc.
- Cloud Platforms & BaaS: Vercel (deployment, serverless functions),
 Supabase (PostgreSQL, authentication, storage), Firebase (authentication,
 Firestore, cloud storage)
- Tailwind CSS
- Animations: Framer Motion
- Git, GitHub and Version Control
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery etc.
- Graphic & Web Design
- Video and Sound Editing
- 2D & 3D Animations
- Content Creation & HR Management

EXPERIENCES

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Gooseberry Innovations

2023-Present

- Front-end Website Development and Design
- Software Project Management

CHIEF EXECUTIVE OFFICER (CEO)

LearnOn - Online Education Platform
December 2020-December 2023

- Content Creation
- Video Editing and Animation (Adobe Premier Pro, After Effects etc.)
- Graphic Design (Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Canva etc.)
- Human Resource Management
- Script Writing & Monitoring Team Activities
- Sound Designing (Adobe Audition etc.)
- Planning & Budgeting
- Managing Social Media and SEO

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Cloudville (Social Managing Company)

July 2020-January 2021

• Graphic Design and Animation

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (BSC)

University of Rajshahi

Major: Applied Physics and Electronic

Engineering

CGPA: 2.86 out of 4 Passing Year: 2013

HSC

Rajshahi Model School And College

Major: Science CGPA: 5 out of 5 Passing Year: 2008

SSC

Rajshahi Model School And College

Major: Science CGPA: 4.75 out of 5 Passing Year: 2006

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

- Bangla
- English
- Hindi

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name: Dipok Kumar Das

Mother's Name: Kolpona Das Date of Birth: Jan 12, 1992

Gender: Male

Height (Meter): 1.651

Weight (Kg): 63

Marital Status: Unmarried Nationality: Bangladeshi

Address: Park Gate, Betia Para, House no. 35, Rajpara, Rajshahi

Blood Group: O+

COURSES

- DATABASE DESIGN & MANAGEMENT
 - Dept. of CSE, Rajshahi University (6 months)
- Hi-Tech Park on C# .NET MVC Dept. of CSE, Rajshahi University (6 months)
- Cisco Certified Network Associate
 (CCNA) Dept. of CSE RUET (1 year)

REFERENCES

REFERENCE 1

Dr. Shaikh Enayet Ullah

Professor and Ex-Chairman

Department of Applied Physics and Electronic Engineering,

University of Rajshahi, Rajshahi-6205, Bangladesh.

Email: enayet_apee@ru.ac.bd, enayet67@yahoo.com

Cell: +8801731-557967

REFERENCE 2

Dr. B. K. Bose

MBBS, MCPS, MD

FELLOW, NIH, USA

Professor & Director

Institute of Nuclear Medicine & Allied Sciences

Dinajpur

Bangladesh Atomic Energy Commission

P.O Box #07, Dinajpur-5200. Bangladesh

Tel: Off. +880-531-65154

Cell: 01819-436033

Email: bkbosebd@yahoo.co.in

REFERENCE 3

Subrina Zarin

Managing Director

Cloudville (Social Marketing Company)

Cell: +8801735896760

Email: subrinazarin007@gmail.com